http://www.wilentz.com/coronavirus-legal-response-team-resource-center

Whether Business Law or Personal Law, We've Got You Covered
The coronavirus (COVID-19) outbreak continues to evolve, causing disruption and volatility to businesses, families, governments, educational pursuits, and economies worldwide. We know that business clients face unprecedented challenges with respect to essential operating concerns, long-term risk assessment, and complex employee health and safety issues. Personal services clients are impacted by health, economical, educational, childcare, and related concerns. To increase our value and improve client outreach, Wilentz has activated the Wilentz Coronavirus Legal Response Team & Resource Center.  As the pandemic endures, it requires unprecedented adaptation to every area of life, and we continue to update our resources to meet our clients’ needs, as Wilentz has done for 100 years.
Our multidisciplinary legal response team is working with clients to withstand the impact on their businesses and to guide their efforts to reopen, restore, and prosper. In addition, we are tracking legal developments and sharing topical information and our latest thinking through this Resource Center.  Call Us Now: 732.313.2323
Quick Searches
# CARES Act
# Paycheck Protection Program
# Families First Coronavirus Response Act
# Provider Relief Fund
# New Jersey Executive Orders
# Essential Construction Projects
# New Jersey Essential Businesses
required
Add me to your mailing list.
Please refer to our privacy policy and disclaimer before subscribing.
Thank you for your submission. You will receive an email confirmation shortly.
Alerts & Publications
Dec
10
2020
Employer Update: CDC Updates COVID-19 Exposure Quarantine Guidance
The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (“CDC”) has revised its published guidance regarding quarantine time for individuals who may have been exposed to COVID-19.…
Oct
29
2020
What Employers Need to Know About Executive Order 192 and New Jersey’s New Workplace Health and Safety Standards
On October 28, 2020, Governor Murphy signed Executive Order No. 192 which requires “every business nonprofit, and governmental or educational entity...that permits its workforce, whether in part or as a w…
Oct
22
2020
The CDC Redefines the Definition of “Close Contact“
On October 21, 2020, the CDC updated its definition of “close contact."  Close contact now means contact with an individual, within 6 feet, for an aggregate of 15 minutes or more in a 24-hour period.…
Oct
07
2020
New Guidance from Small Business Administration
on Purchase and Sale Transactions Involving PPP Borrowers
Effective October 2, 2020, the Small Business Administration (SBA) promulgated a Procedural Notice identifying the circumstances under which transfers of ownership or assets of companies that have received Payc…
Sep
29
2020
Employers May Defer Payment of Social Security Tax Until 2021 for Select Employees
In order to provide Americans economic relief during the COVID-19 pandemic, President Trump signed an executive order that provides an option for employers to defer the payment of an employee’s share of s…
Sep
21
2020
Department of Labor Updates FFCRA to Only Exclude Certain Healthcare Sector Employees
On September 16, 2020, the U.S. Department of Labor issued a revised definition of healthcare provider, excluding certain jobs within healthcare practices. The updated definition no longer includes: all employe…
View All COVID-19 Alerts
Key Contacts
John Anzalone
Personal Injury Law
732.855.6021
Tracy Armstrong
Employment Law
732.855.6020
732.855.6062
Joseph J. Russell, Jr.
Family Law
732.726.6236
Michael F. Schaff
Corporate
732.855.6047
Jenna N. Shapiro
Family Law
732.855.6164
×
Your privacy is important to us.  This notice explains our privacy policy and the choices you can make about the way your information is used at our website.
Personal Information.  You may generally browse our website anonymously without providing any personal identifying information.  However, we will collect personal information if you provide it to us in the following circumstances:
You request additional information regarding our services or publications or sign up for our newsletters;
You register to attend an event we are hosting;
You submit a Consultation Request form;
You submit a question through our contact form, send us an email through the website, or submit a comment on our blog;
You apply for employment.
We use this information to respond to your requests or inquiries.  With the exception of vendors providing hosting, database management, and development services related to the operation of our website, we will not disclose or sell your personal information unless approved by you or required by law.
Our site contains links to other sites that may have different information practices.  Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.
Cookies and Usage Information Collection.  We may collect details of visits to individual webpages.  The information collected may include browser and device information, referring web page, length of time spent, and pages accessed while visiting our website.  This usage information is collected to help us manage and administer our website, improve the content of our website, and customize and improve the website user experience.
We use cookies to track user preferences.  A cookie is a small data file that certain websites write to your hard drive when you visit them.  If you prefer not to receive cookies through our website, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence.  You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser.  If you choose not to accept cookies, some of the features of our site may be disabled or rendered unusable.
Children under 13 years old are not the target audience of this site.  By making this site available to the public, we do not intend to solicit personal information from these children.  If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide any personal information about yourself to us.
Policy Changes.  We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time.  Please review the policy periodically for changes.  You can email any questions regarding this policy to GC@wilentz.com.
Last Revised: 6/4/2020
